Guide to the Jerome T. Barrett Collection, 1913-2010 LAC0007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- The Friends of Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service History Archive, 1919-2010; Record Group 1; 68.5 Linear Feet
  - General/Institutional, 1946-2010; Record Group 1 Series 2; 23.5 Linear Feet
    - Studies and Reports, 1946-1997; 1974-1997; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5; 2 Linear Feet
      This subseries contains studies and reports relating to the FMCS and other labor mediation topics dating from 1946-1997, with the bulk of the materials dating from 1974-1997. Topics for the studies include FMCS preventive mediation and technical assistance programs, FMCS history, national conference summaries, and unionization among air-traffic controllers.
      - The President's National Labor-Management Conference Summary and Committee Reports, 1946; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 110, Folder 1)
      - Three Year Report of the Labor-Management Committee of the Jamestown Area, 1974 November 11; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 110, Folder 2)
      - "Evaluation of the FMCS's Technical Assistance Program in Labor-Management Relations by Objectives", 1978; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 110, Folder 3)
      - "Impact of the 1974 Amendments to the NLRA on Collective Bargaining in the Health Care Industry," 1, 1978; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 110, Folder 4)
      - "Impact of the 1974 Amendments to the NLRA on Collective Bargaining in the Health Care Industry," 2, 1978; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - "Mediation and Labor-Management Relations in the Federal Government," 1, 1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 2)
      - "Mediation and Labor-Management Relations in the Federal Government," 2, 1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 1)
      - "Mediation and Labor-Management Relations in the Federal Government," 3, 1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 2)
      - Technical Assitance Reports, 1980-1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 3)
      - "The National Mediation Board at Fifty", 1984 December; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 4)
      - FMCS in the Reagan Era Reports, 1985; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 5)
      - "National Evaluation Study of FMCS Cooperative Labor-Management Grant Projects from October, 1984 to December, 1986", 1987 September; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 6)
      - "The Forgotten Promise: The Resurgent Unionism Among the Air-Traffic Controllers", 1988; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 7)
      - Internal FMCS Preventive Mediation Study, 1989; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 1)
      - "Outside Employment and Other Outside Activity", 1990 January 9; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 2)
      - "A Look Back at 1989", 1990 January 17; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 3)
      - "Promoting Labor-Management Cooperation: A National Perspective on State Programs", 1991 December; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 4)
      - FMCS History, 1997; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 5)
      - "An Assessment of the Use of Interest-Based Bargaining and Traditional Bargaining to Facilitiate Labor/Management Negotiations", 1999 August; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Files, 1948-1999; 1975-1985; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6; 12.5 Linear Feet
      This subseries is arranged for the most part in its original order. However, the chronological files and memoranda were placed at the beginning of the subseries.
      Note: Materials in Boxes 129-133 were added after initial processing and follow the same arrangement plan.
      This subseries contains FMCS Administrative Files dating from 1948-1997, with the bulk of the materials dating from 1975-1985. Included are a wide variety of materials detailing the FMCS' day-to-day activities, including meeting summaries and chronological files of correspondence and memoranda, as well as materials from the FMCS' many mediation programs, internal audits, workshops and cooperation efforts with other Federal agencies. Also included are specific FMCS case files and statistics, information on the implementation of new legislation, and materials detailing the FMCS' switch to automated case and data processing. Completing the subseries are a variety of miscellaneous items, including essays, reports, employee surveys, and blank forms.
      - Chronological Files, 1974, 1974 July 1 - August 21; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Chronological Files, 1974, 1974 August 21 - November 13; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - Chronological Files, 1974, 1974 November 13 - December 31; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Chronological Files, 1975, 1975 January 2 - March 31; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - Chronological Files, 1979, 1979 April; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Chronological Files, 1979, 1979 December; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - Chronological Files, 1980, 1980 January; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Chronological Files, 1980, 1980 Februray - April; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - Chronological Files, 1980, 1980 March - July; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Chronological Files, 1980, 1980 July - September; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Chronological Files, 1980, 1980 October - December; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Chronological Files, 1981, 1981 January - February; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Chronological Files, 1981, 1981 March - April; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Chronological Files, 1981, 1981 May - June; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Chronological Files, 1981, 1981 July - September; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Memoranda, 1958 Januray - 1959 June; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Memoranda, 1959 July - 1960 December; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Memoranda, 1961 January - June; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Memoranda, 1962 January - June; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - Memoranda, 1962 July - December; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - Memoranda, 1963 January - June; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Memoranda, 1963 July - December; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Memoranda, 1964 January - June; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Memoranda, 1964 July - December; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Memoranda, 1965 January - June; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Memoranda, 1965 July - December; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Memoranda, 1966 January - June; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Memoranda, 1966 July - December; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Memoranda, 1967 January - June; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - Memoranda, 1967 July - December; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Memoranda, 1968 January - June; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Memoranda, 1968 July - December; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Memoranda, 1969; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Memoranda, 1970; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Memoranda, 1971; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Memoranda, 1972; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Memoranda, 1973 January - June; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Memoranda, 1973 July - December; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Memoranda, 1974-1977; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Memoranda, 1978-1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Memoranda, 1977-1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Memoranda, 1983-1986; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Policy Memoranda, 1957-1965; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Case Control Procedures, 1958; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Case Assignment and Reporting Procedures, 1959-1960; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Unsorted Early FMCS Material, 1958-1969; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Mediator Language Skills, 1963 October 22; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Field Organization and Management Improvement, 1958-1964; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - National Office Staff Meetings [1/3], 1976; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - National Office Staff Meetings [2/3], 1976-1977; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - National Office Staff Meetings [3/3], 1977-1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - Notice Statistics, 1982-1985; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 96, Folder 12)
      - Operations Audit Publications and Plans, 1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Office of Administration Significant Events, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Mediator Transfer Files, 1977-1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Grievance Mediation, 1956-1977; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Management Information Reports, 1983; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Pre-Assignment Procedures, 1974-1978; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Department of Budget and Finance Historical Files, 1971-1973; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - "The Role of the Field in Professional Development", 1977 October 21; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Oral Requests, 1982-1983; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Automated Data Processing Material [1/2], 1982-1984; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - Automated Data Processing Material [2/2], 1982-1984; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - Walter Maggiolo Material, 1949-1969; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Director Horvitz Briefing Material, 1977 May 9-23; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Betty Brock Harrassment Complaint, 1977-1978; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Iowa Beef Processors, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Work-men's Union Mediation Case, 1973-1974; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Independent Truckers Strike [1/2], 1973-1974; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Independent Truckers Strike [2/2], 1973-1974; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Administrative Assistants' Conference, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - Presidential Boards of Inquiry Procedures, 1962-1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Mediator Training, 1976-1978; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 98, Folder 9)
      - Management Planning Seminar, 1978; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Department of Economic Affairs Task Force, 1971 December 10; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1971 March 22 - 1974 May 15; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Jerome Barrett FMCS Director Candidacy, 1993; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - FMCS Management Retreat, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - Dispute and Technical Assistance Case Listing, 1981 February 25; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - National Office Audit, 1975, Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - National Office Audit, 1976 [1/2], Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - National Office Audit, 1976 [2/2], Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - Organizational Audits, 1981-1982; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 99, Folder 8)
      - Operations Audit Review, 1972; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 99, Folder 9)
      - Management Improvement, 1970-1971; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 99, Folder 10)
      - FMCS Office of Technical Services [1/2], 1975-1977; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 99, Folder 11)
      - FMCS Office of Technical Services [2/2], 1975-1976; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - FMCS Employee Surveys, 1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - "A Four Year Review of FMCS Dispute Mediation 1977-1980", 1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Mediation Case Statistics, 1959; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Region III Organization and Case Information, 1978; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Health Care Case Procedures, 1983; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Mediator and Case Statistics, 1955-1959; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Dispute Mediation Data, Fiscal Year 1966, Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Dispute Mediation Data, Fiscal Year 1967, Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 100, Folder 9)
      - Region VII Work Flow Report, undated; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - FMCS Reorganization, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 100, Folder 11)
      - Merging of New York Metropolitan Area Offices, 1978; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 100, Folder 12)
      - Health Care Industry Labor-Management Advisory Committee, 1976; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 100, Folder 13)
      - National and Regional Audit Program, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 100, Folder 14)
      - Civil Service Reform Act Implementation, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 100, Folder 15)
      - New Administrative Assitant Training, 1978-1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - Automated Case Administration [1/2], 1984-1986; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - Automated Case Administration [2/2], 1984-1986; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - Fiscal Year 1985-86 Staffing Plan, 1985 March 28; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - President's Advisory Committee on Mediation and Conciliation Meeting, 1985 April 10; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Delegation of Authority, 1971-1977; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - Directors' Meeting Summary, 1975 August 1; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 101, Folder 7)
      - Regional Boundaries, 1960-1977; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 101, Folder 8)
      - Decentralization of Federal Government Activities, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 101, Folder 9)
      - Travel Policy Workshop [1/2], 1978; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 101, Folder 10)
      - Travel Policy Workshop [2/2], 1978; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 101, Folder 11)
      - Technical Assistance Task Force, 1974-1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 101, Folder 12)
      - Congressional Justification of FMCS Program Requirements, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - Performance Appraisal, 1977-1986; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - Meeting Summaries, 1977-1986; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - Regional Operations Audit Program, 1950-1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - New Mediator Materials, 1958-1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - FMCS Executive Development Program, 1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - Proposed Case Control System Presentation, 1983 January 17; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 102, Folder 7)
      - FMCS Merit Pay and Performance Appraisal System, 1979-1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 102, Folder 8)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 102, Folder 9)
      - Florida A+M Industrial Relations Major Development, 1971-1973; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 102, Folder 10)
      - Hopi vs. Navajo Native American Land Dispute, 1974-1976; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 102, Folder 11)
      - Oglala Sioux Tribe Election Report, 1976 February; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - FMCS/Department of Commerce Voluntary Standardization Program, 1976-1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - Federal Highway Administration, 1978-1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - State of Alaska Mediation [1/2], 1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - State of Alaska Mediation [2/2], 1979-1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - American-Iranian Conference, 1976-1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - "Waging Peace" PBS Documentary, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - Automated Case Processing, 1983-1985; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 103, Folder 8)
      - Notice Processing Unit Management Analysis Study, 1985; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 103, Folder 9)
      - FMCS Operations Audit Program, 1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 103, Folder 10)
      - "Progress Report on FMCS' Compliance with OMB's Circular A-123 and with the Federal Managers Integrity Act of 1982", 1983 September; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - Case Reporting Forms, 1969-1970; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - Form Revisions [1/2], 1983; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - Form Revisions [2/2], 1983; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - Blank Forms, 1977-1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - Age Discrimination Act Materials [1/6], 1979-1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - Age Discrimination Act Materials [2/6], 1979-1987; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - Age Discrimination Act Materials [3/6], 1979-1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Age Discrimination Act Materials [4/6], 1979-1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Age Discrimination Act Materials [5/6], 1978-1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - Age Discrimination Act Materials [6/6], 1978-1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Age Discrimination Act Mediation Training, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - "Schucking Off the Rights of the Aged: Congressional Ambivalence and the Exceptions to the Age Discrimination Act of 1975", 1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 105, Folder 6)
        Author: George Alexander
      - "Of the Aged and the Constitution", 1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 105, Folder 7)
        Author: Howard Eglit
      - "The Age Discrimination Act and Youth", 1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 105, Folder 8)
        Author: Lee E. Teitelbaum
      - "The Age Discrimination Act of 1975, As Amended: Genesis and Selected Problem Areas", 1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 105, Folder 9)
      - "The Graying of Civil Rights Law: The Age Discrimination Act of 1975", 1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 106, Folder 1)
        Author: Peter H. Schuck
        Published in "The Public Interest" journal, Summer 1980.
      - "Mediating Civil Rights: The Age Discrimination Act" Report, 1984 July; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 106, Folder 2)
        Authors: Linda R. Singer and Ronald A. Schechter
        Prepared for The National Institute For Dispute Resolution
      - Alternative Dispute Resolution, 1977-1997; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Mediator-Trainee Program, 1972-1976; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - National Academy of Peace and Conciliation, 1977-1982; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - FMCS Mediation Projects and Activities [1/3], 1975-1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - FMCS Mediation Projects and Activities [2/3], 1976-1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - FMCS Mediation Projects and Activities [3/3], 1978-1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - "New Tools for Resolving Environmental Disputes" Report, 1979 October; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - "The Potential of Mediation for Resolving Environmental Disputes Related to Energy Facilities" Issue Paper, 1979 December; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - NAACP vs. Wilmington Medical Center Federal Court Case, 1979-1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 2)
      - Mediator Training and Development, 1975-1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 3)
      - Targeted Selection Training, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 4)
      - Community Conciliation Program [1/3], 1973-1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 5)
      - Community Conciliation Program [2/3], 1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 6)
      - Community Conciliation Program [3/3], 1979-1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 7)
      - Assessment Centers, 1976-1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 108, Folder 1)
      - Congressional Correspondence, 1972-1977; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 108, Folder 2)
      - Environmental Protection Agency Mediation, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 108, Folder 3)
      - Edward Hartfield Materials, 1978-1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 108, Folder 4)
      - Dispute Resolution Act of 1980, 1972-1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 108, Folder 5)
      - Development of Non-Traditional Mediation Programs [1/2], 1977-1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 108, Folder 6)
      - Development of Non-Traditional Mediation Programs [2/2], 1976-1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 108, Folder 7)
      - Region IV Clerical Conferences [1/2], 1958-1964; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 108, Folder 8)